[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this horror film five-year-old Carol communicates with a group of ghosts.", "correct_answer": "Poltergeist", "incorrect_answers": ["A Good Son", "The Ring", "Amityville"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Hall of Fame is located in Cleveland, Ohio?", "correct_answer": "Rock and Roll", "incorrect_answers": ["Hockey", "Basketball", "Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two of the main characters in The Lost Boys were played by these iconic eighties actors who starred together in several other films, including Dream A Little Dream.", "correct_answer": "Corey Haim and Corey Feldman", "incorrect_answers": ["Jami Gertz and Barnard Hughes", "Jason Patric and Kiefer Sutherland", "Dianne Wiest and Edward Herrmann"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which singer led The Nude Tour?", "correct_answer": "Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["Issac Hayes", "Jewel", "Ashanti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the difference between rabbits and hares?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Hares live above the ground.", "Unlike rabbits, hares are born with hair and are able to see.", "Hares have longer ears than rabbits."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the best location to exercise in order to fight depression according to studies?", "correct_answer": "Outdoors", "incorrect_answers": ["In a gym", "In the bathroom", "In your home"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What languages are spoken in Luxembourg?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["German", "French", "Luxembourgish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what scene does George Lucas make his appearance in Episode III: Revenge of the Sith?", "correct_answer": "At the Opera House", "incorrect_answers": ["In the Jedi Council chamber", "On Mustafar", "On General Grievous ship"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who kills Carmen Brown in Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Lieutenant Miller", "incorrect_answers": ["She dies in a car crash", "Blaze", "Her ex-boyfriend"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call these numbers:  0, 1, 4, 9, 16, 25, 36, 49, etc?", "correct_answer": "square numbers", "incorrect_answers": ["algebraic numbers", "cubic numbers", "prime numbers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2006 movie Babel, what happened to Chiekos mother?", "correct_answer": "She jumped off her balcony.", "incorrect_answers": ["She died of cancer at age 37.", "She shot herself.", "She was killed by her husband."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do orphaned grizzly cubs Grinder and Coola live?", "correct_answer": "British Columbia", "incorrect_answers": ["Yukon", "Northwest Territories", "Ontario"]}]